(Penny:)Oh, balls.
(Sheldon:)It's a warm summer evening
in ancient Greece.
(Howard:)Okay, I got a bone to pick with you.
(Leonard:)What did I do now?
(Howard:)I was in bed with Bernadette
and you text-blocked me.
(Bernadette:)-What?
-Yeah, we were completely naked...
...and about to devour each other
when:
[IMITATES CELL PHONE CHIMING]
(Howard:)You text her that I have a problem
with her hanging with you.
(Leonard:)You do have a problem with her
hanging out with me.
(Howard:)But that's not what you tell her.
-What was I to tell her?
-I don't know.
(Howard:)Something that doesn't make me
come off as a petty, jealous douche.
(Leonard:)And what would that be?
(Penny:)Come on,
do I have to think of everything?
(Penny:)Hey, Leonard,
am I too late to see your experiment?
(Bernadette:)-Oh, hi.
-Hi.
(Bernadette:)-What are you doing here?
-Same thing you're doing here.
(Howard:)-Came to see Leonard's experiment.
-No, you didn't.
(Bernadette:)You said Leonard's experiment
was stupid.
[HOWARD SIGHS]